你们猜怎样
Hey, you guys, guess what.
巴瑞和明蒂要离婚了
Barry and Mindy are getting a divorce.
天啊
Oh, my God.
你是怎么搞的
What is the matter with you?
-不  是巴瑞和明蒂  -抱歉
- No. Barry and Mindy. - Oh, sorry.
我一听到"离婚"  就以为是罗斯
l hear "divorce," l immediately go to Ross.
谁是巴瑞和明蒂
Who's Barry and Mindy?
巴瑞是我差点要嫁的人
Barry was the guy that l almost married,
明蒂是我最要好的朋友
and Mindy was my best friend.
当初他不就是被你跟她乱搞吗
Wasn't he cheating on you with her?
是啊  但只表示
But that just means
他做爱时睡死在她身上  而非我身上
he was falling asleep on top of her instead of me.
天啊  要是我真的嫁给他
God, could you imagine if I actually married him?!
我的人生会多么不同
I mean how different would my life be?
我懂你的意思
I know what you mean.
我总是在想
l've always wondered how different my life would be...
要是我没有离婚会怎样
...if l'd never gotten divorced.
-哪一次  -第一次啦
- Which time? - The first time!
真的  想象一下要是卡萝没变成同性恋
Seriously, imagine if Carol hadn't realized she was a lesbian.
想象不出来  我一直想到女女
l can't. l keep seeing it the good way.
我肯定还在练控手道[空手道]
l bet l'd still be doing my karate.
我们婚姻后期  我经常练控手道
Towards the end of our marriage, l did a lot of karate.
好宣泄我缺乏...
It's a way of release the tension from...
缺乏某些"肉体"运动的多余精力
... not doing anything else physical.
也许你不念成控手道就没事了
Maybe the problem was you were pronouncing it "ka- ra- tay."
如果我还是很胖呢
What if l was still fat?
你一定不会跟我交往
You wouldn't be dating me, that's for sure.
-当然会  -少来了
- Sure l would. - Come on.
你们真的觉得我那么肤浅吗
You guys really think l'm that shallow?
不  我只是觉得摩妮卡太胖
No, l just think Monica was that fat.
要是我没被《我们的岁月》开除呢
Hey, imagine if l'd never got fired off Days of Our Lives.
卡萝又出现了
Hey. Hey, there's Carol again.
要是我有勇气辞职呢
What if l had had the guts to quit my job?
我没准就在帮《纽约客》写稿了
l'd probably be writing for The New Yorker,
拿钱搞笑
being paid to be funny.
现在的工作也很有趣啦
But my job's fun too. l mean,
明天...  我不必打领带
tomorrow...l don't have to wear a tie.
要是我答应了去美林证券上班呢
What if l'd taken that job at Merrill Lynch?
-什么  -美林证券
- What? - Merrill Lynch?
对  我有个客人在那里上班
Yeah, l had a massage client who worked there,
他说我有炒股票的头脑
and he said l had a knack for stocks.
那你怎么不去
Why didn't you take the job?
因为当时我相信
Because at that time, you see,
押韵的事情都会成真
l thought that everything that rhymed was true.
我觉得要是我去做股票
So l thought if l worked with stocks...
就得住地窖
...l'd have to live in a box
只能吃安眠药  养三脚猫
and only eat lox and have a pet fox.
你们觉得如果人生真的如刚才所说的
Do you guys think if all those things happened,
我们还会在一起吗
we'd still hang out?
天啊  瑞秋·格林
Oh, my God. Rachel Green?
劳勃·提尔曼
Rob Tilman!
不对  是我  罗斯
No, no, it's me. Ross.
对不起  罗斯·提尔曼
Oh, l'm sorry. Ross Tilman.
不是  是罗斯·盖勒
No. No, no. Ross Geller.
-对哦  莫妮卡的哥哥  -没错
- Of course! Monica's brother. - Yeah. Right.
-你好吗  -很好  我结婚了
- Wow! How are you? - Good. Good. l'm married.
我也是
Me too!
-结婚真好不是吗  -是啊  超棒
- lsn't it the best? - Oh, it's the best.
-莫妮卡好吗  -非常好
- So how's Monica? - Really, really great.
事实上她就在前面街那
Actually, she's right down the street.
要不过去打个招呼吧
You know what? You should stop by and say hi.
-好啊  -她会很高兴
- l would love to. - Yeah, She'd be so excited.
-好  -走吧
- Okay. - Come on.
等等  你是不是忘了付你
Wait, don't you have to pay for...
《巨乳女郎》的钱了
...Busty Ladies?
没关系
No, that's okay.
是有个小孩托我帮他买啦  不过...
Some kid asked me to pick it up for him, but l....
是吗  好吧
Oh yeah? Okay.
莫妮卡  你还在跟无聊医生交往吗
So, Monica. Still going out with Dr. Boring, huh?
他才不无聊  他只是...
He's not boring. He's just....
只是比较低调
He's low-key.
-给  你的榛果拿铁  -谢谢
- Here you go, one hazelnut latte. - Thank you.
其实榛果不是果实
You know, the hazelnut, actually not a nut.
而是种子
lt's a seed.
还有谁能说出一种常见种子
Can anyone else name a well-known seed
被当成果实[疯子]的例子吗
that's been masquerading as a nut?
天啊  我想想看
Oh, dear God. Let me think.
你怎么了
What's the matter?
我又被退稿了
l got another rejection letter.
他们说我的东西很有趣
They said my writing was funny,
只是不符合《阿奇漫画》风
just not "Archie Comic" funny.
亲爱的  我得回医院了
You know what? Honey, l gotta get back to the hospital.
好
All right.
-再见  -再见
- Bye. - Okay. Bye- bye.
对了  答案是巴西果
By the way, the answer is: the Brazil nut.
他的原问题是  "有东西比他还无聊"吗
Was his question, "what's more boring than him?"
老兄  退稿的事真遗憾
Hey, man. Sorry about the Archie thing.
你要我给你点钱吗
You need me to give you some money?
我穷归穷  但骨气还是有的
l may have no money, but l still have my pride.
是吗
Really?
也许乔伊不必给你钱啊
Maybe Joey doesn't have to give you the money.
-电视明星都有助理对吧   -好主意
- TV stars have assistants, right? - That's an idea.
要是我请助理转交  你会收吗
lf l hire an assistant, would you take money from her?
不是啦  钱德勒可以当你的助理
No, Joey. Chandler could be your assistant.
他可以帮你回信给影迷
He could answer all your fan mail and stuff.
不错  就这么办吧
That would be great! Let's do that!
我有钱领  还有时间写作
l could use the money. It could give me time to write.
-那就行啦  欢迎加入  -感谢
- All right. Great. Welcome aboard! - Okay!
我现在要去上厕所啦
All right. Now, l need to use the bathroom.
不过我上厕所不用人帮
Since l don't need any assistance in there,
-助理你就休息吧  -好的
- take a break! - All right.
菲比
Hey, Phoebe.
-你猜怎样  -怎样
- Guess what. - What.
乔伊找钱德勒当他的助理
Joey just hired Chandler to be his assistant.
真好
That's so sweet.
等一下  等我一下
Oh! Hang on!
等我一下
Hang on!
说
Go!
不对  不对  我是说一到50点就卖
No. No, no. l said sell when it hits 50!
50是一个数字  在49后面
Five- oh! lt's a number! lt comes after four- nine!
没关系  没关系
No, it's okay. lt's okay.
一次错误可以接受
You're allowed one mistake.
开玩笑的  你当然被开除了
Just kidding. You are, of course, fired.
莫妮卡
Hey, Mon?
你看我遇见谁了
Mon, look who l ran into!
天啊  瑞秋
Oh, my God, Rachel!
-你好漂亮  -你也是
- God, you look terrific! - So do you!
-你是不是瘦了  -你真贴心  居然注意到了
- Did you lose weight? - You are so sweet to notice.
没错  我瘦了3.5磅
Yes, l lost 3 1 \2 pounds!
记得我的朋友钱德勒吧
You remember my friend Chandler.
-那位是菲比  -你好
- And that's Phoebe over there. - Hi.
天啊  快坐下  坐下
Oh, my god! Sit down, sit down.
我们多久没见面了啊
How long has it been since we've seen each other?
上次是1987年  圣诞节第二天
1 987, the day after Christmas.
西恩·麦克曼的派对
Sean McMahan's party.
我弹了我的创作曲给你听
l played you one of my songs,
"星际求爱仪式"
you know, "lnterplanetary Courtship Ritual."
对  没错
Oh, yeah. Right.
-你还在玩音乐吗  -偶尔吧
- So, now, do you still do music? - Well, sometimes.
-找时间来我家  我弹...  -天哪
- You should come over sometime. l'll play you- -  - Oh, my God!
《我们的岁月》的主演乔伊·崔比安尼
Joey Tribbiani from Days of Our Lives
居然走了进来
just walked in here!
瑞秋  他是我们的朋友
Rach, he's a friend of ours.
你们是德雷克·拉莫瑞医生的朋友啊
You're friends with Dr. Drake Ramoray?
要跟德雷克交朋友有点难呢
lt's hard to be friends with Drake...
因为他很忙  又是个虚构人物
...because of his busy schedule and the fact that he's not real.
我也可以把我的电子琴带过来
Hey, or l could bring my keyboard here sometime.
-他过来了  -乔伊
- He's coming over. - Joey?
好啦  拿去
l know. Here, here.
不是啦  这是我朋友瑞秋
No. This is my friend Rachel.
我们是高中同学
We went to high school together.
我好喜欢你演的戏
l...I love you on that show.
我每天都看
l watch you every day.
你的前妻明明想杀你
I mean when you took out your own kidney to save your ex- wife...
你还捐肾救她...
...even though she tried to kill you....
遇见影迷总是很开心
lt's always nice to meet fans.
-她不是疯子吧  -不是
- She's not crazy, is she? - No.
所以...你好吗
So how you doing?
等一下
Hang on.
等一下  等一下
Hang on. Hang on.
说
Go!
谁
Who's this?
好  你会爱上替我工作的
You're gonna like working for me.
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
布伦蒂是什么鸟名字
What kind of name is "Brindy"?
我... 随便
I...Whatever...
闭嘴
Stop talking.
好  从今天开始你就叫琼安
All right, from now on your name is Joan.
姓给你自己选
You can pick your own last name.
-你在这里  -惨了  是老板大人
- There you are. - Uh- oh, it's my boss.
这是你今天该做的工作表
Alright. Here's a list of things for you to do today.
我们会合作很愉快的  太谢谢你啦
And this is gonna be so great. Thank you so much.
我要去片场了  今天要接生双胞胎
l gotta go to work. l'm delivering twins today,
但只有一个是我的骨肉
but only one of them is mine.
"把衣服送去干洗  去拿我的维他命
"Drop off my dry cleaning. Pick up my vitamins."
教我怎么写维他命
"teach me how to spell vitamins."
把我的新牛仔裤穿软"
"wear in my new jeans."
你知道你是什么角色吧
You realize what you are don’t you?
什么角色
What?
你是他的小喽啰
You’re his bitch.
不   不
No, no! No!
等等  你不会是坐坏了我的巧克力棒吧
Wait! You didn't sit on my Kit Kats did you?
不是  股市小幅震荡
No, there was a little, little dip in the market...
我损失了1千3百万
...and l lost 1 3 million dollars.
不过巧克力棒没事吧
But the Kit Kats are all right?
怎么办   怎么办
What am l gonna do? What am l gonna do?
通知公司  我会被杀
l can't call my office, they'll kill me.
通知客户  他们会自杀
l can't call my clients, they'll kill themselves!
-妙啊  现在还胸口痛  -什么
- Great, now my chest hurts. - What?
我的胸口在痛
My chest hurts.
现在喘不过气来了
And now l can't breathe.
菲比  你是心脏病发作吗
Pheobe, are you having a heart attack?
如果是  左臂会来回抽痛吗
lf l were, would l have shooting pains up and down my left arm?
-会  -那就是了
- Yes. - Then, yes. That is what l'm having.
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
别这样  菲比  没那么糟糕
Come on, Pheebs, it's not that bad.
一般人如果可以休息两星期
Most people would be excited
会放鞭炮庆祝呢
if they didn't work for a couple weeks.
一般人不喜欢他们的工作  我喜欢我的工作
Most people don't like their jobs. l love my job.
我才休息三小时
l've been not working for three hours,
我就快疯掉了
and l'm already going crazy.
我都想念琼安了
l miss Joan.
你心脏病发
Honey, having a heart attack is
是老天在告诉  你该放慢脚步
nature's way of telling you to slow it down.
我一直以为心脏病发
l always thought having a heart attack
是老天在表示  你该死了
was nature's way of telling you to die.
但是你不会死
But you're not gonna die.
你迟早会死
l mean, you are going to die,
但不是今天
but you're not gonna die today.
我去死了算了
l wish l was dead.
我们出去走走
Let's take a walk.
你应该考虑去替
Maybe you should consider writing for
《讲话不经大脑》杂志写稿
Talking Out of Your Ass magazine.
你最近怎么样
So what's going on with you?
我练控手道练得更勤了
Well, l've been doing a lot more of my karate.
-跟卡萝还在无性期吗  -对啊
- Still a dry spell with Carol? - Yeah.
你们多久没上床了啦
How long has it been since you've had sex?
-上个周末...  -那还好嘛
- Well, last weekend... - Oh, that's not so bad.
就满两个月...
...will be two months...
放弃尝试后的两个月
...since l stopped trying.
也许你应该玩一点刺激的
You need to spice things up.
-例如什么  -不知道啊
- What do you mean? - l don't know.
你们可以玩玩情趣捆绑啊
You could tie her up. She could tie you up.
可以在对方身上吃东西
You could eat stuff off each other.
淫言秽语  3P  性爱玩具
Dirty talk, menage a trois, toys.
角色扮演
Role- playing.
你当典狱长她当囚犯
You're the warden, she's the prisoner.
你当海盗她当村姑
You're the pirate, she's the wench.
好  我懂了
Okay, l think l got it.
或者你们都扮演股票经纪人
Or you could be two stockbrokers,
在证劵交易所里的交易大厅
and you're rolling naked on the trading floor...
赤身裸体在大家面前滚床单
and everybody's watching.
纯属虚构
lt never happened.
那里是布瑞帝酒吧
And all right, over there is Brady's Pub...
我行完医都喜欢去那里轻松一下
...where l like to unwind after a long day of "surgeoning."
好棒喔  还有呢
This is so amazing. What else? What else?
那是一个大型电视台设备
Well, that is a large piece of television equipment.
那是一个老男人
And that is an old man.
老男人  你好
Hey, old man!
参观完毕  要不要回我家继续参观
Alrighty. What do you say we head back to my place?
我很想去  但是不行
You know, l would really love to, but l shouldn't.
为什么  为什么
Why? Why...
世界不能停止转动
can't the world stop turning...
只要一下下  只为了我们
just for a moment, just for us?
那不是戏里的台词吗
lsn't that a line from the show?
对  不过
Yeah, but...
我或许说过同样的话  但是...
I may have said those things before, but...
只有这一刻...
...l never truly meant them...
我才是真心的
until now.
那也是戏里的台词
That's a line from the show too!
你看太多电视了
Okay, you watch too much TV.
乔伊  你要的现榨柳橙汁来了
Joey, here's the freshly squeezed orange juice you asked for.
谢谢
Thanks.
里面有果肉
There's pulp in that.
怎么了
Yeah.
我们不是讲过了
l thought we talked about this.
我不喜欢果肉  不要果肉
l don't like pulp. No pulp.
果肉不是果汁  我要纯果汁
Pulp isn't juice. All juice. Okay?
对不起  我就是喜欢果肉
l'm sorry. l guess l just like the pulp.
天啊  抱歉  我没顾及到别人的感受
Oh, my god. l'm sorry. l am being so rude.
瑞秋  你要喝汽水什么的吗
Rachel, would you like a soda or something?
钱德勒会马上去帮你买
Because Chandler will run right out and get it.
好啊  就冰红茶吧
Yeah, well, sure, iced tea would be great.
冰红茶
lced tea.
好  那您要什么吗
Okay. Anything for you, sir?
我刚才不是说了吗
Did l not just tell him?
钱德勒  你想替我工作
Okay, look, Chandler, if this is gonna work...
就要专心听我说话啊
...you have got to listen.
你要拿果汁泼我  对不对
You're gonna throw that juice at me, aren't you?
这不是纯果汁
lt's not all juice.
老婆  早上很好玩吧
So, honey, this morning was fun, huh?
我们洗澡时  我对你饿虎扑羊
Me hopping in on you in the shower there?
是啊  也许以后可以换一个
Yeah, maybe someday we could get a place
有两间浴室的房子
with two bathrooms.
卡萝  我在想或许
Look, Carol, l was thinking maybe....
我们可以玩一点刺激的
Maybe we can spice things up a little.
-怎么说  -卡萝  我们的性生活不美...
- What do you mean? - Carol, our sex life. lt's just not- -
-爸  -你在啊  小伙子
- Dad! - Hey there, little fella!
你要不要去穿鞋鞋
Why don't we get some shoes on you, huh?
你自己去房里穿鞋鞋
Why don't you show Dad how you can put your shoes on
-给爸爸看  好不好  -好
- in your room. Yeah? - Yeah!
说真的  我们的性生活...
Seriously, our sex life.
我想说或许...
l was thinking maybe, l don't know...
我们可以换个新花样玩玩
...we could try some new things, you know, for fun.
-像什么  -我不知道
- Like what? - Well, l don't know.
例如我们
What if we were to...
玩玩捆绑  如何
...tie each other up?
有些人会在对方身上吃东西
Some people eat stuff off one another.
不好
Yeah.
我们可以说淫声浪语助长情趣
You know, we could try dirty talk.
-我们可以玩3P  -这个我喜欢
- We could have a threesome. - l love that idea!
谁的故事被《阿奇漫画》采用了
Who sold a story to Archie Comics?
天啊  太棒了
Oh, my God, that's so great.
你是个发表过作品的作家了
You're a published writer.
真希望我准备了贺礼给你
l wish l had a present for you.
等等
Wait a minute.
我的最后一个巧克力棒
My last Kit Kat bar.
-我们一起吃好不好啊  -好啊
- You want to share it? - Okay!
钱德勒  我知道你很生气
Chandler, l know you're mad.
但我想跟你道歉
But I just want to say l'm sorry.
我太混蛋  太过分了
l was a total jerk. Completely over the line.
但我就是讨厌果肉
l just.... l hate pulp.
你知道莫妮卡是如何看待低脂美乃滋的吗
You know how Monica feels about low-fat mayonnaise?
那不是美乃滋
lt's not mayonnaise!
总之
Okay. Anyway,
我只想说对不起  这个给你
l just wanted to say l'm sorry, and here.
什么东西
What's this?
现榨的柳橙汁
Fresh- squeezed orange juice, with pulp.
-有你喜欢的果肉  -谢了
- Just the way you like it. - Thanks, man.
乔伊
Hey, Joey.
钱德勒的故事被《阿奇漫画》采用了
Chandler sold a story to Archie Comics.
天啊  太棒了  恭喜
Oh my god! That's great! Congratulations!
是什么故事啊
What's the story?
也没什么
You wouldn't care.
只是个白痴的漫画故事
lt's just a stupid comic book story.
开什么玩笑
Are you kidding me?
我最爱阿奇那票人了
l love Archie and the whole gang.
阿奇需要钱修他的老爷车
Well, Archie needs money to fix his jalopy.
但他不想跟瑞吉拿钱
But he doesn't want Reggie to just give him the money.
所以瑞吉就找他当助...
So Reggie hires him as his assist- -
当管家
As his butler.
然后叫他做一堆无聊事
And then makes him do crazy things...
例如叫他买不能有结块的奶昔
...like bring him milk shakes that can't have lumps in them.
等等  有点耳熟喔
Wait a minute. That sounds a little familiar.
这个故事画过了吧  我觉得我读过了呢
Did they already do that one? l think l read it!
莫妮卡  我一定要问
Monica, listen. l have to ask.
乔伊·崔比安尼
Okay, Joey Tribbiani
约我去他家
invited me back to his apartment.
他经常找女人去他家吗
Does he do this with a lot of girls?
对  经常  超级经常
Yeah, a lot. A lot, a lot.
而我是其中之一个幸运儿
And l'm one of them.
我真不敢相信  这可是乔伊·崔比安尼啊
l just cannot believe this. l mean, Joey Tribbiani.
虽然与我无关
You know, it's none of my business, but...
但你不是结婚了吗  对啊
aren't you married? Yeah.
我有一点点希望我们还没有结婚
l wish we could just not be married for a little bit.
真希望我们能分开一下
You know, l just wish we could be, like, on a break.
可惜你们不是
Well, you're not.
你当然轻松  你又没结婚
So easy for you. I mean, you're not married.
爱跟谁上床就跟谁上床
You can have sex with whoever you want.
是啊  没错
Yeah, l can.
别以为我没有哦
And don’t think I don’t, because I do!
我一天到晚都有
l mean, all the time. You bet!
莫妮卡
Monica?
你有那方面的经验了吧
You've...you've done it, right?
当然有
Of course l have.
你以为我是个三十岁的老处女吗
What do you think, l'm, like, some 30- year- old virgin?
天啊
Oh, my God.
你是个三十岁的老处女
You're a 30-year-old virgin.
要不要那么大声  怕后面那人听不到吗
Say it louder. The guy in the back didn't hear you.
我听到了
Yeah, l heard it.
我不是没有机会
lt's not like l haven't had the opportunity.
我只是在等完美的对象
I mean, l'm just waiting for the perfect guy.
我正在跟罗杰交往
l keep seeing this guy Roger.
他虽非完人
He's not perfect...
但是  或许我在想要不要将就一下
but l'm thinking maybe l should get it over with.
把我的"花蕊"给他
You know, give him my flower.
天啊  那就给吧
Oh, my God, do it!
你等得够久了
Honey, you've waited long enough.
你说得对  没错
You know what? You are right.
没必要把性看得那么严重
Yes. Sex doesn't have to be a big deal.
性爱不该有任何规则和限制
There shouldn't be all these rules and restrictions.
人应该随时随地
You know, People should be able to sleep
想跟谁上...
with whoever they want, whenever- -
瑞秋  我永远不会
Rachel, l'm never gonna think it's okay
支持你背叛你老公
for you to cheat on your husband.
你懂什么啊  处女
What do you know, virgin?
菲比
Phoebe?
厕所怎么有烟冒出来
Why is smoke coming out of the bathroom?
医生说可能会有这种副作用
The doctor said that could be one of the side effects.
菲比  把烟熄掉
Phoebe! Put the cigarette out.
不  那不是香烟
No, it's not a cigarette.
烟是从我身上冒出来的
The smoke is coming out of me!
-熄掉  -好啦好啦
- Put it out. - Okay, okay!
-真高兴有你们在  -躺好
- l'm so glad you're here. - Come on.
-我来接  -给我
- l got it. - Give it to me!
- l got it. - Give it!
喂
Hello?
她现在不方便接电话
No, she can't come to the phone right now.
好  没问题  再见
Right. No problem. Okay, bye- bye.
是公司吗   他们生气吗
Was it my work? Were they mad?
是杰克吗   他有嚷嚷吗
Was it Jack? Did he yell?
别紧张  没有人嚷嚷
No, just relax. Nobody yelled.
杰克只是打来问你有没有好转
Jack was making sure you were getting better.
谢天谢地
Thank God.
她被开除了
Yeah, she's fired.
你已经尽力了  卫斯理医生
You've done all you can, Dr. Wesley.
该放手了
You've got to let her go.
别了  好好安息吧
Goodbye and Godspeed, Hope Brady.
且慢  卫斯理
Not so fast, Wesley.
拉莫瑞
Ramoray!
没错  卫斯理
That's right, Wesley.
我只是来说
l just stopped by to say that
你不配当真正的医生
you're not a real doctor.
那个女人的脑部好得很
And that woman's brain is fine.
太好了
Oh, thank God.
-霍普  霍普  -德雷克
- Hope? Hope? - Drake.
霍普  你不会死
You're not dying, Hope.
你会从此过着幸福快乐的日子
You're gonna live a long, healthy life.
与我共度一生
With me.
德雷克
Oh, Drake.
好  我决定了
Okay.
好
Here we go.
乔伊  我是瑞秋
Hi, Joey? lt's Rachel.
我明天晚上有空
l am free tomorrow night.
没问题  我可以带三明治去
Yeah, sure, sure, l can bring some sandwiches.